This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
With help from Jinbei, Luffy makes his way to the scaffold,
only to be halted by the Navy's three admirals.
When it seemed all was lost, Whitebeard and his men joined the fray.
Now an all-out battle has broken out between the Navy's elite
and the strongest pirates in the world.
Go, Ice Block! Party, son!
Go! I'll fight!
I'm counting on you, son!
You're full of courage, aren't you?
But take this word of advice.
If you're simply not strong enough,
you won't even come close to saving him.
He's nothing but a big-mouthed kid
who goes to the Navy's elite.
You're full of courage, aren't you?
But take this word of advice.
If you're simply not strong enough,
you won't even come close to saving him.
He's nothing but a big-mouthed kid
who goes looking for trouble.
Dumb and clumsy.
Careless, too.
But I've got a soft spot for fools like him.
You, you're always sailing around wreaking havoc.
But here, you're through.
That's what you think.
Hang on, Ace.
I'm coming for you.
If you want to reach the scaffold,
you're gonna have to make it through me first!
The power that will shorten one's life.
Energy Hormone Redox.
We're up against him, too!
The legendary hero, Garp!
He may be over the hill now,
but 20 years ago,
that guy went neck and neck with Gold Roger.
He might be the strongest Marine the Navy has ever seen.
He didn't just fight Gold Roger,
he beat his rival, too.
When Sheiky the Golden Lion
launched his attack on Marineford,
Garp was the one who locked him up in Impel Down.
We didn't make it all the way here
just to lose to an old man!
Legends ain't nothing but words.
I might say the same thing to you, Whitebeard.
Your glory days are just a dying memory now!
Oh, please!
Damn.
Are you gonna destroy this entire city?
Send me the bill for repairs when we're done.
This is ridiculous!
Just execute him!
Alright, go and get a substitute immediately!
Sir!
Megapad!
Keep pushing toward the scaven!
Ironic, I know, but I forgot about those things!
No more lasers for today!
Enough!
Did you think we were weak, Link?
We're from the New World!
Those are tits!
Get to the scaven!
How is he?
It isn't good.
First aid isn't going to cut it, I'm afraid.
We gotta get him out of here and fast.
The odds were against him from the start,
but this is too cruel.
He's so close!
A final moment of regret?
Poor boy.
Cold Roger?
Yeah, of course I know who he is.
But who gives a crap?
People talk like he's something special,
but what did he even do?
He just riled up a bunch of criminals.
And thanks to that bastard,
the entire world is screwed up.
And what does that mean?
There's no way you're that stupid.
Everyone knows before he was executed,
he told some BS story about hidden treasure
to give the middle finger to the government.
But either way, it worked,
cause a bunch of dumb pirates
bought into the whole thing and went nuts.
Don't you get it?
He left behind a stain people still can't clean up.
Even killing the bastard wasn't enough.
Now, thanks to him,
we gotta put up with a bunch of human garbage
pissing on everyone else following his lead.
He's the biggest piece of crap who ever lived.
He stinks even after we flushed him.
Just like you, kid.
Did I hurt your wittle feelings?
Are you in the Roger fan club?
You got something you wanna say, kid?
Ah!
What was it this time?
Everyone's making a fuss about some thugs that got beat near to death by a kid.
That's too bad. I was hoping they would die.
Don't give me that!
You realize when you pull this kind of crap, I'm the one who gets chewed out for it, right?
Hey, are you listening?
Honestly, I don't know what that old fool was thinking leaving a boy like you with me.
What? You want me to tell you about Roger?
Hmm. Huh.
He was a liar. And a murderer and a miserable thief to boot.
Only jackasses believe his crap.
King of the pirates, king of the chumps, he's dead either way.
Got that right.
Roger, huh?
I'm trying to enjoy a drink over here, kid.
The man was a hack. Now piss off.
Hear me? Beat it, kid.
Hey! What do you think you're doing, you little punk?
I should see the other guy, right?
Look, Ace. You can't keep doing this, kiddo.
So your grandson, he's around my age, huh?
Uh-huh.
Do you think he's happy with himself?
Luffy? I think he is.
The boy's growing up in fine feather.
Old man.
Tell me the truth.
Did I deserve to be born or was it just a mistake?
That's not for me to say.
You just keep living and hope you find out.
Quick, carry Straw Boy back to the ship.
It's not ideal, but we'll have to save Ace Boy without him.
I need one last favor from you.
We're coming for you, Ace.
We're taking you home.
That Navy never stood a chance.
This is wrong.
My friend, don't lose hope.
I swear I shall save your life no matter how much blood it's filled.
We're almost there.
There's no stopping us now.
Don't let them get you down, Ace.
Yeah, we won't leave you.
We're brothers. We stick together.
Dammit, this is all wrong.
How the hell am I supposed to feel?
Pops, Luffy, my friends.
They're here to save me,
but they're pushing through a sea of their own blood to do it.
Don't say one last anything.
We're getting out of here alive, darn it.
You know what I need.
Hmm?
I'm sick.
These are tears of joy.
Even after all I've done,
I want to live.
Eva, help me.
You realize what the repercussions of this would be, don't you?
Uh.
Captain Buggy.
He's awake!
He's alive!
I knew it all along!
Ah, jeez, what happened?
We okay?
Aokiji just froze you solid.
It was really freaky.
Captain Buggy!
Oh, no!
It's too late!
No!
He was so beautiful, so perfect!
He was gonna conquer the world, damn it!
The world!
Oh, no!
He got hit by the ice attack on purpose
so he could show us how to unfreeze everyone else!
Even when he's frozen solid,
he's still thinking of his friends!
Quick!
Let's blow out the other guys before it's too late!
Okay!
Stay drowning over here!
I want to rescue your savior first!
Remember, I can swim!
Help!
Captain Buggy!
We were blinded by your godlike glory
and forgot about the whole devil fruit thing!
You saved us so many times!
And we almost let you down!
I'm sorry!
Sue me!
I'm not omnipotent, but as long as you still worship me,
we're good!
Looks like I've still got my luck and my lackeys!
By the way, where did Mr. Three run off to?
I'm not sure.
The last time we saw him was before those walls trapped us in here
and everything went to hell!
That little rat, he made it out, didn't he?
You mean these walls?
With the cannons?
The Navy lured everyone in, then trapped them with these things.
After that, it was ice and meteors and boiling water,
and, well, we're trapped.
Oh, are we?
Because the great Captain Buggy wouldn't have made it this far in life
if he'd surrendered every time he ran into a measly wall or two.
You hear that, Navy?
Buggy's coming for ya!
No walls, ice, or giant magma fists can stop me!
Awesome!
You've only been defrosted like a couple of minutes,
but you're like, bam, let's do it!
That's how I roll.
Okay, seriously, now what?
Better move, my punk!
Son of a...
Are you okay?
The ravages of time humble us all.
Yes, even you.
Screw the fight, this is what I was afraid of.
I don't want no sympathy.
There's no way I'm wearing this crap in front of my enemies.
Damn it, Pops.
Huh.
Wouldn't turn your back on me if I were you.
Marco!
You're gonna make the same mistake.
Jojo!
Someone has to seize you off.
And that duty seems to have fallen on me.
Pops, no!
Whoa!
Got good!
Aw, crap!
Hey!
It's a little late for a change of heart now.
No offense, but they don't need you anymore.
I mean, I think we all know the Navy's got this one.
Akainu got Whitebeard,
Kizaru took out Marco and Aokiji froze Josu.
You wouldn't kick a man while he's down,
so don't run out there just to pick up scraps.
And if you were looking to test yourself against Straw Hat again,
he's out too.
Even the strongest pirates in the world got stomped.
Good to know we're on the winning team this time.
Because I promised myself that I'll keep trying.
Till...
Till I become a Marine Admiral!
No!
I'm sorry!
I got carried away!
This is so embarrassing.
I just want to dig a hole and bury my head in it.
That was really airing into me.
I got worked up after seeing you again, and I just...
Kobe.
You said you're gonna fight me, right?
Then you will become that strong.
You'll have to.
I'm so ashamed of myself even thinking that.
It was obviously a pipe dream from the start.
Even with all his strength,
Luffy couldn't make his dream come true.
But at least he fought.
All I've done is run.
I don't even pass as a Navy soldier, let alone an Admiral.
It's useless.
I'm useless!
Come on, you should be happy.
Our team just scored a massive victory.
I bet they'll throw a party.
Another hormone shot?
Do you want to die?
You're past your limit.
I'm sorry, kid.
But you've been burning your candle at both ends for too long.
Have you forgotten that poison you suffered through?
You cheated death once.
I didn't save you so you could destroy yourself.
I told you this last time.
My hormones aren't a magic fix-me-up you can take every time something goes wrong.
I want to save Ace Boy just like you.
But if you keep misusing my power like this, you'll die.
As long as I do everything I can.
I don't care if I die.
I'm begging you, you have to let me fight.
Guys, I think Pops is down.
Marco!
Josu!
If I don't keep fighting, then they kill Ace because I wasn't there for a-
Then I'd rather be dead anyway!
Right now, it's the only fight that matters, live or die!
You dummy!
Whatever would I tell your dear old dad Dragon if I let you die like a dog due to my deadly devil fruit power!
This stubbornness of yours is not cute at all!
Where's the replacement?
What could possibly be taking him so long?
Well, it was short notice and we don't do this very often.
Hey!
You ready?
Fine, let's move.
Ace!
Oh fine!
It's your life!
Give us a good show!
Wait!
What are you doing?
No way!
Kisaru hit him dead on!
It's a miracle he's even alive, let alone getting up and screaming like that!
Wait!
Where do you think you're going?
You'll get home!
Kobe!
I won't run away!
Luffy!
heedless of his injuries, yet even with his sudden strength,
he faces a wall of marines blocking the path to Ace.
Among them, an old friend appears for a reunion
neither of them expected to come so soon.
On the next One Piece, to live up to a promise,
Luffy and Kobe collide.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!